[{"id": 1518, "question": "Women had a significant part to play during World War II,which was the time when women also made their own contributions.Some women's great efforts and their names have been recorded in history.Here's a look at some of the strong figures of women in World War II. Tatiana Nikolaevna Baramzina was born in Glazov of Russia on December 12,1919.In 1943,she was sent to the Central Women's Sniper Training School and upon her graduation in April,she was further sent to the front.She managed to kill around 16 enemies in the first three months!Unfortunately,she was captured by the enemies and was killed on the fifth of July in 1944.Today,the street where she grew up has been renamed in her memory. Anne Frank was a Germanborn Jewish girl who was wellknown for the publication of her diary that describ...\n\nQ: Who were killed by the enemy in the war?", "options": ["Tatiana Baramzina and Anne Frank.", "Hannah Szenes and Tatiana Baramzina.", "Anne Frank and Margaret Ringenberg.", "Margaret Ringenberg and Hannah Szenes."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2887, "question": "A month after Hurricane Katrina, I returned home in New Orleans. There lay my house, reduced towaist-high ruins, smelly and dirty. Before the trip, I'd had my car fixed. When the office employee of the garage was writing up the bill,she noticed my Louisiana license plate. \"You from New Orleans?\"she asked I said I was, \"No charge.\"She said, and firmly shook her head when I reached for my wallet. The next day I went for a haircut, and the same thing happened. As my wife was studying in Florida, we decided to move there and tried to find a rental house that we could afford while also paying off a mortgage (> on our mined house. We looked at many places, but none was satisfactory. We'd began to accept that we*d have to live in extremely reduced circumstances for a while, when I got a very curi...\n\nQ: The garage employee's attitude toward the author was that of  _", "options": ["unconcern", "sympathy", "doubt", "tolerance"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 631, "question": "In the US and Britain, the slogan around colleges was \"Save water. Shower with a friend.\" Now, Wuhan University has come up with another system for the campus bathhouse. It charges students for the amount of time in a shower. Before entering the bathhouse, students pay for the amount of time they want in the shower with cash or their student ID card. The clock starts ticking the minute the tape is turned on. It pauses when a button is pressed for soap. An integrated circuit (IC) card reader at each tap shows the time. No money, no water. The benefits of the new system can be seen with the old system, which charged 1 Yuan for each person regardless of time in the shower. The university used about 320 tons of water daily under the old system, but only 160 tons now. Many students use the new ...\n\nQ: It can be inferred from the passage that   _  .", "options": ["the new operation can raise students' environmental awareness", "the new operation can solve the water crisis", "a similar operation has been set in other universities", "the university has saved a lot of water by using the new system"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 1164, "question": "What's A Real Friend? You can have the same neighbors for years. You love them or you think you love them. And you hope that they love you. But do you ever really understand them? Charlie Kemp and his family lived next door to me for 15 years. We were good friends all the time. I enjoy friendship. I think it's the best thing in the world. And friendship with the Kemps was easy because they seemed to welcome it. They were interesting and clever people. Their house caught fire twice, and twice the whole family slept in mine. They are always losing things like money, keys and watches. Pictures fell off the walls, the children fell out of bed ... I was their neighbor and their friend. Life was always interesting, never dull. Best of all, I liked the whole family. One day, I lit a fire in the g...\n\nQ: The author was blamed by the policeman because   _  .", "options": ["he was found burning the rubbish by the policeman", "he was found polluting the environment by burning the rubbish", "his neighbor Charlie Kemp complained about his action and called the policeman", "he burnt something of his neighbors"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1437, "question": "Life is full of sweet surprises for Chinese pop singer Edell. She majored in design in a Canadian college. But when she was looking for a job after graduation, she found herself rising as a star in singing. Then she became a hostess on TV. \"These are roles I never expected to take,\" she said. Edell is open to every possibility in life, not afraid to try new things. She says that every day she tries to get herself ready to take any chance that occurs in life. \"My mom told me chance only rewards those with a prepared mind,\" she said. \"So I've tried to explore my potential talents. Thus I won't be at a loss when the right opportunity comes up.\" Edell learned ballet in her childhood until she broke her back in practice. She then fell in love with music. Like many girls of her age, she has a ri...\n\nQ: What is Edell's strongest character?", "options": ["Liking to remember things.", "Liking to help others.", "Liking to think of problems differently.", "Liking to try new things."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2084, "question": "I am sure that everybody in his/her life has used computers. Nowadays you can feel their presence everywhere at home,at school,at work and they certainly make life easier.On the other hand,there are people who can't work with them. Anyway,I believe their presence is a good thing. Life with them seems easier, less difficult and more comfortable You can use them to choose your meal,to withdraw your money, and also save your time,because these operations are all controlled by computers. Therefore you can hardly imagine the modern world without them;the whole planet seems to be one big computer society. Nevertheless,problems can often appear in this area, too.To have a computer means you have to be quite well-off and have the necessary skills to use it.However,think about questions like \"Are c...\n\nQ: The writer's main purpose in writing the passage is  _", "options": ["to encourage us to use computers in our society", "to advise us to say no to computers from now on", "to remind us to care about the problems that computers bring.", "to inform us that the computer has become a necessary part of our life"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 3468, "question": "My father was poor in expressing his feelings. I knew that my dad loved me, but showed me love in other ways. There was one particular time in my life when this became real to me. I always believed that my parents had a good marriage, but gradually the strain on my mom and dad's relationship was quite evident. However, I was not prepared for the day when Dad had decided to leave. All that I could think of was that I was going to become a product of a divorced family. I kept telling myself that it wasn't going to happen. The night before he left, I stayed up in my room for a long time. I prayed and I cried and I wrote a long letter to my dad. I told him how much I loved him and that I would always and forever be his Krissie. As I folded my note, I stuck in a picture of me with a saying I ha...\n\nQ: How did the author feel when her father decided to leave?", "options": ["Excited.", "Annoyed.", "Doubtful.", "Upset."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 3256, "question": "Teachers and textbooks _ -- your future could be under threat from a quickly developing and very smart technology. University of California researchers led by Jacob White hill recently programmed teaching robots to react to facial expression. Whitehill's achievement marked a major step forward in the way people could one day learn by establishing facial expression recognition in robot teachers. The teaching robots or, Intelligent Tutoring Systems (ITS) are computer systems that provide personalized instruction and feedback to students without human intervention. The facial expression recognition allows a computer to react according to expressions a user makes. He said that the system was an important development in improving learning systems. \"Classical ITS typically have a somewhat rigid ...\n\nQ: The writer seems to   _  the newly-developed teaching robots.", "options": ["throw doubt on", "object to", "take no interest in", "approve of"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 3460, "question": "Manage your time well for each module , but also make sure you get a good balance between work and social life. That is for life in general. Set aside time specifically for each subject. Try to study one subject a day. You need to balance time. If you are bad at balancing things, make a personal timetable. Even if you do not stick to it, you will have an idea what you should be doing each day. This is better than trying to do everything each day and, at the end of the week, not achieve anything. Also, try to keep your weekends free of studying. Only study at the weekend if you really have to. I had to learn to balance work, study and family when I was at college. I was a retail assistant working part-time and had at least four modules to complete at the same time at college. I also had to ...\n\nQ: According to the passage, which of the following is NOT the advice the writer gives?", "options": ["Try to study many subjects in a day.", "Try not to study on the weekends.", "Plan in advance.", "Try to set a timetable."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2324, "question": "Starting college can be a difficult experience. You have to deal with new responsibilities, growing independence, a challenging course load, and of course, the social scene. When a roommate is thrown into the mix, it may feel like you're struggling with all that stuff while living in a small box with a stranger. But having a roommate doesn't need to be one more thing to worry about. When students go into their living situations with realistic expectations and a willingness to _ , things can work out just fine. When you first meet your roommate, chances are that you'll be on your best behavior. You want to get along since this is the person who's going to be sharing your living space for the next year. But try to think ahead to potential worst cases, too. For example, imagine it's 2 am and ...\n\nQ: When you go to college you have to   _  .", "options": ["learn to look after yourself", "quarrel with others often", "take care of a stranger", "throw yourself into a separate room"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 544, "question": "Yueyang Tower lies in the west of Yueyang City, near the Dongting Lake. It was first built for soldiers to rest on and watch out. In the Three Kingdoms Period, Lu Su, General of Wu State, trained his soldiers here. In 716, Kaiyuan of Tang Dynasty, General Zhang Shuo was sent to defend at Yuezhou and he rebuilt it into a tower named South Tower, and then Yueyang Tower. In 1044, Song Dynasty, Teng Zijing was stationed at Baling Jun, the ancient name of Yueyang City. In the second year, he had the Yueyang Tower repaired and had poems by famous poets written on the walls of the tower. Fan Zhongyan, a great artist and poet, was invited to write the well-known poem about Yueyang Tower. In his A Panegyric of the Yueyang Tower (<<>> ), Fan writes: \"Be the first to worry about the troubles across t...\n\nQ: When did Yueyang Tower become more famous?", "options": ["In 1045.", "In 716.", "In the Three-Kingdom Period.", "In the Tang Dynasty."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2238, "question": "Once upon a time two brothers who lived on neighbouring farms fell into conflict. It was the first serious one in 40 years of farming side by side, sharing machinery, and trading labor and goods as needed . Then the long cooperoration fell apart. It began with a small misunderstanding and it grew into a major difference, and finally it exploded into an exchange of bitter words followed by weeks of silence. One morning there was a knock on John's door. He opened it to find a man with a carpenter's toolbox. \"I'm looking for a few days' work\" he said. \"Perhaps you would have a few small jobs here and there I could help with. Could I help you?\" \"Yes,\" said the older brother. \"I do have a job for you. Look across the creek at that farm. That's my neighbor, in fact, it's my younger brother. Last...\n\nQ: Which of the following is NOT true according to the passage ?", "options": ["The younger brother used his bulldozer to dig a creek .", "After the conflict John was angry with his younger brother.", "At first the carpenter planned to build an 8-foot fence as John asked him to.", "The two brothers made peace at last ."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1120, "question": "Last week, I bought an alarm system for about $ 450. It consisted of a control unit with three other small units. I put the control unit in the sitting room and fastened the other units by the front door, back door and living-room windows. The instructions told us to choose three numbers, so we chose 491, the last three numbers of our telephone number. Now I must explain how the alarm works: 1. There is a power siren in the control unit. It makes a very loud noise. 2. Each of the small units sends out beams or rays in different directions. If anything moves, it breaks a beam. This sends a signal to the control unit. The siren makes a noise that you can hear 50 meters away. 3. When we go to bed, I press the three buttons numbered 4, 9 and 1. Then we have 30 seconds to get out of the room be...\n\nQ: The writer bought an alarm system to  _  .", "options": ["make sure that he got up early every day", "warn him when there were lizards in his house", "frighten burglars and tell him that somebody had got into the house", "make Mary feel safe to live in the large room"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1088, "question": "Coaches and parents always tell us to keep our goals in mind when we go for a competition. Carrying your goals and expectations into a competition is one of the biggest mistakes any athlete can make. This is a big game and you want to win. You want to score a hundred, defeat your competitors, or score a hat-trick of goals. When you carry your goals into the competitive ground with you, chances are great that you will leave that performance with disappointment and heartache, and nothing more! Expectations will _ Expectations will distract you from the performance and make your muscles tighten up. Want to perform to your potential when it counts the most? Then write your goals on a piece of paper before you leave for the game, match or race, and then leave that paper at home! Make a deal wit...\n\nQ: According to the author, expectations and goals should be   _  .", "options": ["set within one's capabilities", "used as an encouragement when training", "written down in case of being forgotten", "divided into some small parts"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 455, "question": "Does your local town have a nickname ? If so, what does it say about the area and the people who live there? Many cities are recognized across the world by their unofficial names. New York is the Big Apple, London is the Big Smoke, and Los Angeles is famously called La La Land. A project has been carried out to make a survey on how the nicknames of some places came about. The University of Winchester's Professor Bill Lucas is a patron of the English Project. He explains that unofficial place names often show what people think about a place. \"The name that people create for a place forms a connection with feelings,\" he says. Basingstoke is a town in central England. The local nickname, Amazingstoke, shows the love that locals seem to have for the area. Swindon, on the other hand, is sometim...\n\nQ: It can be inferred from the passage that   _  .", "options": ["every famous place has a nickname", "the town Swindon must be a clean place", "sometimes nicknames can help save lives", "Rick Stein nicknamed Padstow Padstein"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 591, "question": "It's a fact that we all dream. Some dreams seem to last for hours, others only for seconds. Some of us have strange dreams, some have interesting dreams, and some of us have unpleasant dreams. Tests in the 1980s showed that these dreams occur within 90-minute cycles, each cycle made up of six stages. In the last stage people experience rapid eye movement, known as REM, and it is in this stage that dreaming takes place. Eighty percent of people who were woken during this sixth stage could easily remember their dreams. On the other hand, when during the first five stages (NREM), only seven percent could describe a dream. However, of these same people woken during the first five stages, 74% were able to remember thinking activity, although they would not call it a dream. NerysDee, who has wri...\n\nQ: \"Insomniacs\" are persons who  _  .", "options": ["can always remember their dreams", "have trouble getting into sleep at night", "experience rapid eye movement", "usually wake after each 90-minute sleep period"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 3472, "question": "The story goes that some time ago,a man punished his 3-year-old daughter for wasting a roll of gold wrapping paper.Money was tight and he became infuriated when the child tried to decorate a box to put under the Christmas tree.Nevertheless,the little girl brought the gift to her father the next morning and said,\"This is for you,Daddy.\" The man was embarrassed by his earlier overreaction,but his anger flared again when he found out the box was empty.He yelled at her,stating,\"Don't you know,when you give someone a present,there is supposed to be something inside?\" The little girl looked up at him with tears in her eyes and cried,\"Oh,Daddy,it's not empty at all.I blew kisses into the box.They are all for you,Daddy.\" The father was crushed.He put his arms around his little girl,and he begged f...\n\nQ: The father remembered the love of his daughter by  _  .", "options": ["kissing the gold box", "putting gold into the box", "taking out an imaginary kiss from the box", "keeping the little girl's gold box by his bed"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1935, "question": "Claressa was getting ready for a fight. She had boxed many times before. But this time, the prizes were higher than ever. If she won this fight, Claressa would win a spot on the US Olympic Women's Boxing Team. The fight was difficult. Claressa was up against a two-time US champion. \"Her whole game plan was to hold me against the ropes so I wouldn't hit her,\"says Claressa. Claressa didn't give up. She won the fight. And that wasn't all. She also won the title of outstanding fighter for the whole tournament! Claressa, now 17, started boxing when she was just 11. She was inspired by her dad. He had been a fighter when he was younger. But when she first told her dad that she wanted to box, he didn't support her. \"He told me, 'No! No! Boxing is a man's sport,'\" Claressa remembers. \"It made me s...\n\nQ: The passage is mainly about   _  .", "options": ["a valuable competition of Claressa", "the background of Claressa's career", "the process to Claressa's success", "Claressa's promising boxing career"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2519, "question": "A young man went to a town and worked there. He did not have a wife and a servant did the work in his house. The young man liked laughing a lot. He nailed the servant's shoes to the floor on Monday, and then laughed, because he put his feet in them and fell down. The servant was not angry, but smiled. Then the young man put brushes in his bed on Tuesday. The servant got into bed and hit the brushes with his feet. He was afraid. The young man laughed loudly again. Again the servant was not angry, but smiled. Then on Wednesday the young man said to his servant, \"You're a nice, kind man. I am not going to be unkind to you again.\" The servant smiled and said, \"And I'm not going to put any more mud from the street in your coffee.\"...\n\nQ: When the young man played a joke on him, the servant was not angry but smiled because   _  .", "options": ["he liked the young man' s action", "making the young man laugh is his job", "he was afraid to be fired", "he thought he shouldn't be angry with a child"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 471, "question": "VINCOUVER (Reuters)----South Korea' s Kirn Yuna can finally relax and does fiot need to think about the future after she won the gold medal in the women' s figure skating on Thursday. The 19-year-old was the overwhelming favorite to finish top of the podium but said the pressure going into the event was large. \"I feel now as if a huge burden has been lifted, \" the Games' highest-earning female athlete-she makes an estimated $8 million a year --said after her near-perfect program where she nailed all of her 11 jumps. \"I will enjoy this moment and think about things later.I was just thrilled on the podium and I feel so relieved.I had been running toward this dream of the Olympics and was so happy to be here, \" she said. \"Since I have achieved the most important goal in my life.I am going to ...\n\nQ: According to the passage, Kim Yuna  _  .", "options": ["had a strong sense of team spirit in the Games", "won the first gold medal for South Korea in the Winter Olympics", "had expected she would surely win the gold medal", "joined in the competition with great pressure from her country"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2417, "question": "John and Booby joined a wholesale company together just after graduation from college the same year. Both worked very hard. After several years, however, the boss promoted Bobby to the position of manager but John remained an ordinary employee . John could not take it any more, so he sent his resignation and complained that the boss did not value hard working workers but only promoted those who said good words of him. The boss knew that John worked very hard for the years. He thought for a moment and said, \"Thank you for telling me, but I have a request. I hope you will do one more thing for our company before you leave. Perhaps you will change your mind and take back your resignation.\" John agreed. The boss asked him to go and find out anyone selling watermelons in the market. John went a...\n\nQ: We can conclude from the story that   _  .", "options": ["one should stop his job if the boss doesn't think much of his work", "it's necessary to know the market when you buy a watermelon", "detail plays a very important part in one's success", "one should get along well with his boss if he wants to be promoted"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1056, "question": "Mrs. Allen's husband died ten years ago when her son and daughter were still in high school. Mr. Allen had left some money, and since Mrs. Allen had managed a bookstore before she was married, she took the money and bought a shop in town. Later she moved the shop out to the shopping center. She was a pleasant woman; she worked hard and was well-informed about books, and so the bookstore prospered and she was able to hire a friend to help her. Laura Barnes, Mrs. Allen's friend and assistant, was also a widow. She had some free time and the need for a little extra-money, and so she took the job in the bookstore. She was too clever and friendly, and the two women were well-known in the neighbourhood as \"Mrs. A\"and \"Mrs. B\"....\n\nQ: Which of the following is true?   _  .", "options": ["Mrs. A set up her bookshop in the shopping center", "Mr. Allen was dead but Mr. Barnes alive", "Mrs. A managed to set another bookstore with Mrs. B", "The two children of Mrs. A were of the same age"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 3273, "question": "Europe is now the biggest market for organic food in the world, having grown by 25 percent a year over the past 10 years. Denmark's agriculture minister is herself an organic farmer. The UK market for organic food grew by 55 percent in 2000, while the food market as a whole grew by only one percent. Yet only seven percent of British shoppers account for nearly 60 percent of organic sales. However popular the idea of organic farming may be, it is still an interest for only a few people. So what makes the idea of organic farming popular? Organic farming means farming with natural materials, rather than with man-made fertilizers or pesticides . Organic farmers rely on many methods -- such as crop rotation and the use of resistant varieties, because they are necessary for organic farmers to _ ...\n\nQ: What can we know about organic farming?", "options": ["It refers to farming with natural materials, instead of chemical fertilizers.", "It refers to farming with chemical fertilizers rather than natural fertilizers.", "It refers to farming with soil rather than any other thing.", "It refers to growing crops with man-made fertilizers and pesticides."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2171, "question": "Mark Twain left school when he was twelve. He had little school education. In spite of this, he became the most famous writer of his time. He made millions of dollars by writing. His real name was Samuel Langhorne Clemens, but he is better known to all over the world as Mark Twain, his penname. Mark Twain was born in 1835 and he was not a healthy baby. In fact, he was not expected to live through the first winter. But with his mother's care, he managed to survive. As a boy, he caused much trouble for his parents. He used to play jokes on all his friends and neighbors. He didn't like to go to school, and he often ran away from home. He always went in the direction of the nearby Mississippi. He was nearly drowned nine times. After his father's death, Mark Twain began to work for a printer, w...\n\nQ: In the later years of his life, Mark Twain   _  .", "options": ["wrote many stories and earned a lot of money", "must have been very sad because he lost his family", "continued writing until his death", "lent too much money to others"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 138, "question": "Dear Earthmen , I have enjoyed my stay on your interesting unusual planet. I think I understand the life on earth now and I would like to give you my impressions. First of all you live in boxes. Every morning you leave your big boxes and get into smaller boxes on wheels. All these small boxes race around and around, and finally stop to rest. You then leave these boxes on wheels and go to very large tall boxes. After testing all days you get back in your little boxes and return to your big boxes. There you sit and stare at tiny glowing boxes with moving pictures on the front. Only one thing puzzles me. One day I went to a football game. A bunch of angry boys fought over a little round ball. Everyone yelled for them to stop but they kept on fighting. They were angry, I suppose, about being c...\n\nQ: In the football game  _  .", "options": ["the players were very angry because there was only one ball on the playground", "the man from the Mars thought the players were fighting", "the man from the Mars saw a fighting among the angry boys", "the players were very angry because everyone yelled at them"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 57, "question": "A desert is a beautiful land of silence and space. The sun shines, the wind blows, and time and space seem endless. Nothing is soft. The sand and rocks are hard, and many of the plants even have hard needles instead of leaves. The size and location of the world's deserts are always changing. Over millions of years, as climates change and mountains rise, new dry and wet areas develop. But within the last 100 yeas, deserts have been growing at a frightening speed. This is partly because of natural changes, but the greatest makers are humans. Humans can make deserts, but humans can also prevent their growth. Algeria Mauritania is planting a similar wall around Nouakchott, the capital. Iran puts a thin covering of petroleum on sandy areas and plants trees. The oil keeps the water and small tre...\n\nQ: People in some countries are fighting a battle against   _  .", "options": ["the growth of deserts", "the disappearance of desert plants", "natural changes", "congenital climate"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 3296, "question": "Active vacations are often the most relaxing of all. But Wait! It's all in defining what an active vacation is. We don't expect you to take up jogging, backpacking, or hang gliding. we ask the sedentary vacationers to spend two to four hours a day doing things, such as walking the city streets, exploring a nature preserve, or taking a leisurely rowboat ride. These kinds of activities aren't just good for your physical health. They improve your mental health, even your spiritual health. And they make vacations memorable and worthwhile. Here are some fresh ideas for active and healthy vacation. Make the morning your activity time. At that time it is most likely that the weather will be friendlier, your energy level higher, and your schedule emptier than later in the day. Have a walk at dawn ...\n\nQ: Which of the following is probably the best title for this passage?", "options": ["Driving Tips", "How to Relax Without cars", "Give up Your Car and Walk", "Make your Vacation Healthy"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 384, "question": "To err is human. To blame the other guy is even more human. Common sense is not all that common. Why tell the truth when you can come up with a good excuse? These three popular misquotes are meant to be jokes, and yet they tell us a lot about human nature .To err, or to make mistakes, is indeed a part of being human, but it seems that most people don't want to accept the responsibility for the problem. Perhaps it is the natural thing to do .The original quote about human nature went like this: \" To err is human, to forgive, divine .\"This saying mirrors an ideal people should be forgiving of others' mistakes. Instead, we tend to do the opposite -find someone else to pass the blame on to. However, taking responsibility for something that went wrong is a making of great maturity. Common sense...\n\nQ: What is the author's opinion about a good excuse?", "options": ["Making a good excuse is sometimes a better policy.", "Inventing a good excuse needs creative ideas.", "A good excuse is as rewarding as honesty.", "Bitter truth is better than a good excuse."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1969, "question": "For some people, the prospect of starting college, especially going away to school, is scary. It's probably the first time that you'll be totally responsible for your own schedule. What if you intend to go to college but just don't feel ready to start yet-for whatever reason-and you don't want to take on a full-time job after graduation? You might want to take a year off to pause and regroup. This practice is common in some countries, like the United Kingdom, where it's called a \" _ \". Taking time off doesn't mean you should ignore the idea of applying to college. In fact, you may want to consider making your college plans before you become involved in other things, especially if you'll be travelling. Apply to schools and make your choice, then ask for a deferred admission. Rachel took a y...\n\nQ: Going on a \"gap year\" means   _  .", "options": ["asking for a year's leave to rest at home", "taking a year off to pause and regroup", "ignoring the idea of applying to college", "travelling around the world before going to college"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1046, "question": "Children will find it more difficult to buy cigarettes as vending machines selling tobacco will be officially banned in England today.According to the British Heart Foundation(BHF),around 200,000 young people start smoking regularly in England each year and 11 per cent of l1-to15-year-old regular smokers in England and Wales get their cigarettes from vending machines. Betty McBride, Director of Policy and Communications at the British Heart Foundation,said,\"Thousands of children who are at risk of addiction regularly get tobacco from these machines,which of course,don't ask them to prove their age.With the tobacco industry increasingly depending on young smokers to keep their profits,they're fighting tooth and nail to stop any changes that might hit their bottom line.\" The ban, which makes...\n\nQ: What is the best title for the text?", "options": ["Cigarette vending machines banned", "The youth's addiction to tobacco", "UK's efforts to improve people's health", "Strong opposition from tobacco industry"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2290, "question": "Recreational tree climbing is taking root in the ecotourism industry, and it's sending guys like Tim Kovar to far off reaches of the globe. Kovar, a tree-climbing instructor, recently returned to the U.S. from Brazil, where he spent time developing a tree-climbing operation thanks to the \"slow travel\" movement. Slow travel, is like the slow food movement, the practice of giving fast food in favor of homegrown cooking--the kind that takes hours to prepare and enjoy. Likewise, slow travel urges visitors to experience a place's natural surroundings and learn about the ecology in a way not afforded by extreme games. \"Tree climbing is a slow activity,\" says Kovar. \"It's not something you do quickly and then you're on to the next thing or event.\" There is no such thing as a quick climb, especial...\n\nQ: What do slow travel and the slow food movement have in common?", "options": ["They take people a long time.", "They are related to the eco-tourism industry.", "They advocate protecting nature.", "They cost people little money"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2719, "question": "Holiday houses in Mallorca sailing and fishing port - quiet even in summer season. Beautifully situated houses with sights of sea and mountains, yet near to shops and restaurants. Cars and bicycles for hire. Sailing and sports clubs nearby. ITALY IN COMFORT Luxury coach( - carriage) trips of Italy, out of normal holiday season. 21days to visit five Italian cities starting from London 1 st May, 1 st September . The trips are guided by profess or Martin Davis. Head of Italian Studies, London University . See the arts and culture of historic Italy. KIBBUTZ HOLIDAYS IN ISRAEL Working holidays on a kibbutz( co -operative farm) in Israel. All nationalities welcome for one to three months, if prepared to work morning with kibbutz members. Accommodation , food and trips to historic sights all prov...\n\nQ: The best holiday for Jack and Mary would be  _  .", "options": ["the 21 - day coach trip of Italy", "the 2 -week stay in the Hotel Splendid", "the 14 -day trip around a Caribbean island", "the working holidays for 1 -3 months on a kibbutz in Israel"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 848, "question": "Even if you are a good high-jumper, you can jump only about seven feet off the ground. You cannot jump any higher because the earth pulls you hard. The pull of the earth is called gravity. You can easily find out the pull of the earth. If you weigh yourself, you will know how much gravity is pulling you. Since there is gravity, water runs down hill. When you throw a ball into the air, it falls back down. Because of gravity, you do not fall off the earth as it whirls around. Then, can we get away from the earth and go far out into space? Now you can do it, because spaceships have been invented. Then spaceship will go so fast that it can escape the earth's gravity and carry you into space....\n\nQ: When you slip  you always fall to the ground because  _", "options": ["the earth always turns round.", "the earth has gravity", "the earth's gravity is greater than your weight.", "you are careless."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2503, "question": "When animals and plants use color1 to be noticed it is called advertising color1ation .Advertising color1ation can be used to either warn or attract animals. The bright color1s of flowers and berries are advertising color1ation that attract animals.Flowers need to be pollinated to reproduce.Bees and hummingbirds are attracted to bright color1s and will pollinate the flowers.Some pollinated plants will produce berries.These berries will turn a bright color1 when they are ripe.The bright color1 lets berry-eating birds know the fruit is sweet and safe to eat.After birds eat the berries,the seeds will pass through their digestive system and be left behind.Some of the seeds left behind will grow into new plants! Color is also used to attract mates. Many male birds like the northern cardinal are...\n\nQ: Which of the following would the writer probably agree with?", "options": ["female northern cardinal may have color1ful and bright feathers.", "Red - eyed tree frogs sleep during the day with their eyes open.", "the striped skunk use white stripes to attract their animals", "the color1 of the ladybugs tells meat-eating animals they taste terrible"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 472, "question": "VINCOUVER (Reuters)----South Korea' s Kirn Yuna can finally relax and does fiot need to think about the future after she won the gold medal in the women' s figure skating on Thursday. The 19-year-old was the overwhelming favorite to finish top of the podium but said the pressure going into the event was large. \"I feel now as if a huge burden has been lifted, \" the Games' highest-earning female athlete-she makes an estimated $8 million a year --said after her near-perfect program where she nailed all of her 11 jumps. \"I will enjoy this moment and think about things later.I was just thrilled on the podium and I feel so relieved.I had been running toward this dream of the Olympics and was so happy to be here, \" she said. \"Since I have achieved the most important goal in my life.I am going to ...\n\nQ: It is known from the passage that  _  .", "options": ["Kim Yuna is a person of great confidence", "Joannie Rochette joined in the games with great sorrow", "Kim Yuna is the richest athlete in South Korea", "Mao Asada took silver medal by accident"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2586, "question": "According to the dictionary definition of 'create',ordinary people are creative every day. To create means to bring into being,to cause to exist something each of us does daily. We are creative whenever we look at or think about something in a new way. First,this includes an awareness of our surroundings. It means using all of our senses to become aware of our world. This may be as simple as being aware of color1 and texture ,as well as taste, when we plan a meal. Above all,it is the ability to notice things that others might miss. A second part of creativity is an ability to see relationships among things. If we believe the expression,there is nothing new under the sun,the creativity is remaking or recombining the old in new ways. For example,we might do this by finding a more effective w...\n\nQ: What does the author think about the relationship between a new thought and its being put into practice?", "options": ["It's more difficult to create a new thought than to use it in practice.", "To find a new thought will clearly lead to the production of a new thing.", "A man with an excellent ability of practice can easily become an inventor.", "One may come up with a new thought,but can not put it into practice."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 20, "question": "Today, whether or not you follow the latest trends, one's fashion and choice of dress is a reflection of one's individual style and tastes. Can you still remember how you dressed at the start of China's opening-up? Today's program is one of a special series commemorating the 30th anniversary of reform and opening-up in China. In these two episodes we focused on fashion and style and were honored to invite two special guests to join us in studio--Ms. Zhang Ling from Raffles-BICT Inter-national College and Alex from Esquire magazine. When we talk about fashion, color is absolutely crucial. A color can reflect the mood of an individual person or the spiritual temperament of entire society or age. Mrs. Zhang and Alex talked about the colors which have left the greatest impression on them. In t...\n\nQ: China's opening-up dates back to   _  .", "options": ["the 1960s", "the 1970s", "the 1980s", "the 1990s"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 698, "question": "After their 20-year-old son hanged himself during his winter break from the University of Arizona five years ago, Donna and Phil Satow wondered what signs they have overlooked, and started asking other students for answers. What grew from this soul searching was Ulifeline (www. Ulifeline. org), a Web site where students can get answers to questions about depression by logging on through their universities. The site has been adopted as a resource by over 120 colleges, which can customize it with local information, and over 1.3 million students have logged on with their college ID's. \"It is a very solid Web site that raises awareness of suicide, de-stigmatizes mental illness and encourages people to seek the help they need,\"said Paul Grayson, the director of counseling services at New York U...\n\nQ: One reason that many colleges adopt the website is to   _", "options": ["provide their students with campus information", "offer medical treatment to students in mental disorder", "encourage their students to seek advice about depression", "give their students various help they may need"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1804, "question": "D The year is 2094. It has been announced that a comet is heading towards the Earth . Most of it will miss our planet , but two pieces will probably hit the southern half of the Earth . On 17 July , a piece four kilometers wide enters the Earth's atmosphere with a massive explosion . About half of the piece is destroyed , but the remaining part hits the South Atlantic at 200 times the speed of sound . The sea boils and a huge hole is made in the sea bed . Huge waves are created and spread outwards from the hole . The wall of water , a kilometer high , rushes towards southern Africa at 800 kilometers an hour . Cities on the African coast are totally destroyed and millions of people re drowned . Before the waves reach South America , the second piece of the comet lands in Argentina . Earthqu...\n\nQ: When the first piece hits the South Atlantic , it causes_.", "options": ["an earthquake", "damages to cities", "an Earth explosion", "huge waves"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 3125, "question": "In the last 500 years nothing about people--not their clothes, ideas, or languages has changed as much as what they eat. Chocolate drink was first made from the seeds of the cacao tree by South American Indians. The Spanish introduced it to the rest of the world during the 1500s. And although it was very expensive, it quickly became popular, In London, shops where chocolate drinks were served became important places. Some still exist today. The potato is also from the New World. Around 1600, the Spanish brought it from Peru to Europe, where it soon was widely grown. Ireland became so dependent on it that thousands of Irish people starved when the crop failed during the years of 1845--1846, and thousands more were forced to go to live in America. There are many other foods that have travele...\n\nQ: Chocolate drink was first invented in   _  while coffee was first invented in   _  .", "options": ["Spain; Brazil", "South America; the Old World", "Spain; Ethiopia", "London; Rent"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 554, "question": "Mo Yan, whose primitive name is Guan Moye, was awarded the Nobel Literature Prize on October 11, 2012.\"Chinese author Mo Yan today won the Nobel Literature Prize for writing that mixes folk tales, history and the contemporary,\" the Swedish Academy announced.\"Through a mixture of fantasy and reality, historical and social perspectives, Mo Yan has created a world reminiscent in its complexity of those in the writing of William Faulkner and Gabriel Garcia Marques, at the same time finding a departure point in old Chinese literature and in oral tradition,\" the Swedish Academy said Mo Yan began writing in 1981 and he has published novels, short stories and essays on various topic, and despite his social criticism is seen in his homeland as one of the foremost contemporary authors, the Nobel Com...\n\nQ: Mo Yan is his  _  name.", "options": ["primitive", "pen", "real", "family"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2935, "question": "Scientists estimate that more than 60 percent of cancer deaths in the United States are preventable through lifestyle changes. Although there is no certain way to avoid all cancers, reducing individual risk factors greatly decreases the likelihood of getting many forms of this dangerous disease. The American Chemical Society estimates that smoking causes nearly 30 percent of all cancer deaths in the United States -- that is, about 166,000 cancer deaths each year. All cancer deaths caused by tobacco smoking could be prevented completely by not smoking and not using smokeless tobacco. For those who already smoke, quitting will reduce the risk of developing cancer. Studies show that after about ten years of not smoking, a past smoker's risk lowers to about the level of those who have never sm...\n\nQ: Which do you think is the best title for this passage?", "options": ["The relation between food and disease.", "Causes of different kinds cancers.", "Tips on lifestyle for cancer prevention.", "Ways to remain more healthy."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 895, "question": "Do you want to write your password down so that no one can see it, or do you want to send someone a secret message? Knowing how to make an invisible ink message will have you feeling like a secret agent in no time. These are instructions for making invisible ink using baking soda. Difficulty: Easy Time required: A few minutes What you need: Baking soda, Paper, Water, Light bulb, Paintbrush, Measuring cup, Purple grape juice Here's how: There are at least two methods of using baking soda as invisible ink. Mix equal amounts of water and baking soda. Use a paintbrush to write a message onto white paper, using the baking soda solution as \"ink\". Allow the ink to dry. One way to read the message is to hold the paper up to a heat source, such as a light bulb. The baking soda will cause the writin...\n\nQ: What's the function of the paintbrush?", "options": ["To draw a picture.", "To allow the \"ink\" to appear.", "To write a message onto the white paper.", "To help the \"ink\" dry."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 757, "question": "Among various programs, TV talk shows have covered every inch of space on daytime television. But no two shows are more opposite in content, while at the same time standing out above the rest, than the Jerry Springer and Oprah Winfrey shows. Jerry Springer could easily be considered the king of \"rubbish talk\". The show takes the ever-common talk show titles of love, sex, cheating, and hate, to a different level. Clearly, the Jerry Springer show is about the dark side of society, yet people are willing to eat up the troubles of other people's lives. Like Jerry Springer, Oprah Winfrey takes the TV talk show to its top. But Oprah goes in the opposite direction. The show is mainly about the improvement of society and different quality of life. Contents are from teaching your children lessons, ...\n\nQ: Though the social problems Jerry Springer talks about appear unpleasant, people who watch the shows   _  .", "options": ["show disbelief in them.", "are ready to face up to them.", "remain cold to them.", "are willing to get away from them."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1052, "question": "California places limits on water use to deal with the state's four-year drought. Californians are feeling the heat after Governor Jerry Brown announced an order that puts mandatory statewide water cutbacks into effect. California has faced water-use cutbacks in the past. In January 2014, Governor Brown called for residents to curb their water use by 20 percent, but many places around the state failed to meet that goal. This most recent announcement, however, marks the first time in the state's history that mandatory restrictions have been ordered. Most of California's water supply comes from the Sierra Nevada mountain range snowpack. Normally, during the spring and summer, this snow melts and puts new supplies into groundwater. but this past winter, the snowpack reached its lowest point s...\n\nQ: According to the new order, Californians should_.", "options": ["Water their lawns every three or four days.", "Avoid watering their lawns before rainstorms.", "Take mandatory lessons on water conservation.", "Keep the emergency rules for water use in mind"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2969, "question": "With around 40,000 students, the Politecnico di Milano is the largest and most technical university in Italy, offering undergraduate, graduate and other courses in engineering, architecture and design. Founded in 1863, just two years after Italy was united, Milan Polytechnic is international famous. Many of its graduates now work in big companies abroad like M.I.T., Caltech and Oxbridge. Yet the Politechnic has a problem. As you know, here in Italy people speak Italian. Beautiful though the language may be, it is not a good choice for engineers when they're building a way in Norway or designing a bridge in Vietnam. For better or worse, the global tongue of engineers is English. Hoping to attract more international students, the Politechnic decided to run its doctor's courses in English onl...\n\nQ: The students' attitude towards English-only teaching in doctor's courses is   _  .", "options": ["indifferent", "disapproving", "skeptical", "approving"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 1081, "question": "It's 5pm on a Friday and I'm standing in a coffee shop above Shibuya crossing - one of the most busiest place in Japan where more than a thousand of Tokyo's smartly dressed people gather at eight points, ready to cross - then rush straight for each other. It looks like they must bump into each other, but It's amazing that they all manage to reach the other side safely. But the real reason I'm here is that I want to see people crash. I want businessmen to knock into each other, their umbrellas flying off their arms, and uniformed schoolchildren hitting grannies. Why may I see this now, but wouldn't have had the chance even a year ago? It's very simple - smartphones. Smartphone use is booming in Japan. In 2012, only about a quarter of Japanese used them, most being perfectly happy with their...\n\nQ: How does Michael Cucek find smartphone walk in Japan?", "options": ["He found it by accident when he lives here.", "Japanese pay much attention to their phone manner in public.", "The police in Shibuya are too strict with people's phone manner.", "Smartphone walk in Japan has a deep root."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1806, "question": "Who we are Shanghai Super Star provides combination service including translation and tourism and sourcing, focusing on interpreting and translation. Our professional team offer highly professional business interpreters, assistants, companions and exhibition translators and sourcing for a variety of business requirements as well as tour guides to first-time tourists coming to China. Why choose us ^ Our professional and experienced business interpreters/translators have more than 5 years' experience and also have professional education background like business, foreign trade, management etc. ^ Our knowledgeable and enthusiastic private tour guides are always ready to help design your unique trip. ^ Our reliable interpreters have solid experience in different industries. So we will be your g...\n\nQ: Which of the following descriptions about Shanghai Super Star is NOT true?", "options": ["It serves customers both at home and abroad.", "It can provide business assistants if necessary.", "Interpreting and translation are its main business.", "Its interpreters and translators are all English majors."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1160, "question": "Though I have traveled in hundreds of trains, few unusual things have ever happened to me. But one day in a train something did happen. I do not mean that I was hurt: no one was hurt. I do my work in a hot country far away from England. Every September I go there to do my business, and every July I come back to England to have a rest. So every September I go to Paris and take a train from the great French city to Mendova, and at Mendova I catch my ship. There is one very fast train from Paris to Mendova, and it suits me well. It goes as far as Endoran, but it stops at Mendova for a few minutes to let travelers get out or in. It is called The Flying Bluebird. It reaches Mendova at seven minutes past nine in the morning, and it is never late. A ship leaves Mendova at half past eleven, and so...\n\nQ: On this journey on The Flying Bluebird, the author felt uncomfortable because   _  .", "options": ["he couldn't find a seat by the window", "he was angry with the man sitting next to him", "the window was kept shut all night", "there were too many people on the train"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2522, "question": "\"A good parent\" can be a confusing phrase. It is almost impossible for one person to be \"a good parent\" at all stages of a child's life. Some parents are at their best before their children begin to speak. Others are most successful before their children enter elementary school. Still others make their finest contribution to older children or teenagers. Every parent can understand one stage of a child's development better than another. It is hard for a person to possess superior capacities throughout the entire period of a child's growth. A mother might be \"a good parent\" from her baby's birth until it is three; that is the period when it needs her protection and loving care. Then the start of her child's independence might upset and alarm her, and she might then become less helpful for a ...\n\nQ: Confusion arises about what it means to be \"a good parent\" because   _  .", "options": ["it is normal to be a successful parent during most stages of a child's development", "most parents are only good at helping older children or teenagers", "parents are usually at their best before their children go to school", "parents do not realize they cannot perform equally well through a child's growth"], "answer": 3}]